You made it past numerous
challenges to stand before me.
You deserve praise for—
Shh! My friends will hear us.
H-How dare you?! Do you have any idea who I—
I'm asking you to quiet down.
I do know who you are.
You're a facsimile of
Magic Queen Sildonia Xarles,
who reigned during the ancient magic
kingdom's peak, crafted by the queen herself.
H-How do you know that?
I'll explain later.
Also, we skipped your traps
and riddles to get here.
We dug a shortcut.
How dare you do that to my tomb?!
Anyway, can you see to the final trial?
I'm pulling out the sword.
You know about that too? Just who are you?
You'll see soon enough.
Here we go.
Perfect Reading.
Is this true?
Yeah. You read my memories, didn't you?
I have the Divine Dragon's Heart too.
I don't believe it.
I knew time travel magic existed, but...
Kyle, are you over here?
Not good! My friends don't
know about any of this.
Just follow my lead, okay?
What?
Please!
You're a real pain, you know?
Kyle, what are you doing?
Whoa, a legendary intelligent sword!
And your name is Sildonia Xarles?!
What?
Liese, was it? These treats are quite tasty.
They're just simple provisions
I made before we left.
Say, are you really the magic queen?
To be precise, a part of her.
I am a magic life form created to evaluate
whether you're worthy of my treasure.
And yet you eat treats?
I'm converting them into magic
power to support myself.
They're not going to waste.
Why do you look like a child?
I froze my growth at the age
my magic power peaked.
I looked like this until the day I died.
If you weren't worthy of my treasure,
I would've triggered the final trap
and destroyed the labyrinth,
but you intrigue me.
You have my approval for now.
You may use that sword as you please.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Take that apport bag as well.
It connects to the treasure room,
so it's convenient for getting treasure.
Hey, I use a sword too.
Why not let me use you instead of Kyle?
What?
Physiological incompatibility.
You get rejected for that all the time.
Tastes haven't changed in a thousand years.
Delicious! Just delicious!
You can eat later.
Something smells lovely
at the stalls over there too.
You're like a country kid in
the big city for the first time.
Where are we going now?
Well, we've got our treasure.
So to prepare for our upcoming battles,
we'll need high-quality gear.
Welcome.
Have you business at our shop?
Yeah. I'd like to purchase equipment.
Pardon, but do you have
a referral from anyone?
Oh, right. You need deposits from new
customers before they enter the store.
I'm sorry, but we'll ask a deposit
of ten thousand gadols.
Is five gold Xarles coins
enough for the four of us?
Thank you for your patronage.
Allow me to show you inside.
Welcome. I am Fesba, the shopkeeper.
Ah, this is Melanis's handiwork.
I'm impressed you recognize it.
He was an extraordinary craftsman
of the ancient magic kingdom.
He wasn't that great.
What?
He was rather proud.
He'd tear up when I started
pointing out flaws in his work.
What?
Please, ignore all that.
The kid here's just got a fertile imagination.
Oh, do pardon me.
My, these treats are tasty as well.
This here is our shop's flagship product.
Dragon leather armor, huh?
Yes. In addition to the physical
and magical protections of dragon hide,
we've added heat, cold, and poison resistance.
The lining is made of phoenix feathers,
so you can imagine the price.
Okay, I'll take it.
What? O-Of course...
What about you, Theron?
We'd be matching. Hard pass.
We're getting our equipment here,
so pick out everything you need.
Okay!
What should I get?
It's lighter and easier to move in
than I expected.
Yeah. These gauntlets seem nice too.
A spirit stone amulet, huh?
This is my first time wearing one.
Got any swords that'll make
the babes swoon over me?
Especially babes like you—
I'll bring one right away!
Can I see your magic stones?
Certainly.
For offense, how about these
enchanted with Explosion?
Sounds useful.
Do you have anything highly effective
against reptilian monsters?
But of course, sir.
A Blizzard stone, huh?
Yes. Enchanting stones with cold spells
is tricky, so they're fairly expensive.
We'll take all you've got of both.
Every single one, sir?!
If you've got healing potions,
we'll take all of those too.
All of them?!
It would be a hefty load in coins,
so may I pay with gems as well?
That should be about ten million gadols.
Ten million gadols?!
Thank you very much.
We look forward to your next visit.
Man, that was quite a shopping spree.
I hope no one spreads any nasty rumors.
That won't be a problem.
We'll be leaving tomorrow.
We're only here for a night?
Then I've got no time to waste!
I think I'll take a look around too.
It's not often I'm in the royal capital.
I'll show you around.
I've been here before.
Really? Thanks!
We'll be back.
See you later!
Those two have gotten close.
I feel kind of conflicted about it.
Then I shall be off as well!
I spy tasty stalls over—
Wait. There's something I
want to discuss with you.
While the others aren't around.
Right...
First, I'd like to confirm something.
Is it truly possible to change the future?
That's an odd way to put it.
The future, by definition,
is not set in stone.
What do you mean?
When you traveled back in time,
you simultaneously came to a new world.
This is just my theory,
but there isn't a single timeline.
Time splits into numerous
lines like tree branches.
And your soul jumped
from one branch to another.
As evidence of this, the Divine
Dragon's Heart you used as a catalyst
was also transported here alongside you.
Then if this is a new world, it won't
necessarily follow the same history.
Not identically, at least.
Although the broad strokes will be the same.
At this rate, the Great Invasion
will almost certainly occur.
I see...
Naturally, that's only if you or I do nothing.
It should be possible for us to forge a new
history through our actions and involvement,
though it will probably prove difficult.
Yeah.
That's enough for me.
But wait a minute.
There are two Divine Dragon's Hearts
in this world now, right?
But only one of me.
Yes, I have a theory about that as well.
The most forbidden of magics is a
fusion spell that is never to be named.
Fusion spell?
What is that? I've never heard of it.
Simply put, it's a way to increase
one's magic power by fusing souls.
Increase your magic power?
Your magic power is determined
at birth by the constitution of your soul.
In ancient Xarles, we researched
ways to strengthen souls themselves.
This can be done by fusing them,
but there are many problems with that.
Did you fail?
Indeed. We tried using the souls of infants
and experimented with artificial souls.
Thinking back on it, we feared nothing.
Not even the gods.
But I digress.
There are now two Divine Dragon's Hearts.
So what do you think happened to the soul
of the Kyle Leonard in this world?
What happened to it? You don't mean...
That's right. It's right here.
The soul fusing I mentioned happened
to you without you realizing it.
Your soul should have been strengthened
and your magic power doubled.
Does that ring any bells?
Now that you mention it...
It's possible you'll be able to use
the highest level of spells in the future.
Me, use the highest spells there are?
It's just a theory.
Whether or not you can master
them is another matter,
and all the effects won't
necessarily be good.
Will there be negative effects?
Who knows? This is unprecedented.
So if you notice anything unusual,
don't hesitate to mention it.
I'll gladly give you advice again.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
I've gotten used to camping out,
but beds sure are nice.
Agreed.
You're not going to bed yet, Urza?
No. Every month, I look forward to bathing
in the light of the full moon.
All right. In that case, I'm turning in first.
Good night.
Yeah, good night.
I wasn't sure how it would go at first,
but this trip hasn't been so bad.
Liese is a good girl.
We get along well too.
Sildonia has such vast knowledge, so always
has something interesting to share.
Theron is... well, he's fun to watch.
And then there's Kyle.
He's strange.
He looks at me like he sees right through me.
Yet for some reason,
that doesn't bother me.
No!
I'm the only one... allowed at Kyle's side...
Talking in her sleep?
O great Goddess Muna, bless this journey.
Wait, I totally forgot!
My stamina has improved some,
but I still have a long way to go.
The Phantom Training Method?
We didn't have that in my day.
It doesn't compare to actual battle, though.
This is truly an amazing sword.
It feels like an extension of my body.
Of course it does.
I am the embodiment of
Xarles's magic technology.
There is no greater blade
forged by humanoid hands.
I've used mithril swords before,
but none compared to this.
To be precise, that's not made of mithril.
What? Then...
Kyle!
I... I finally found you.
What's going on? It's late.
The Application of the Contract!
We can only do it now during the full moon!
Oh, I forgot.
You're the one who suggested it!
I know, but...
Let's do it another time.
That would be a month from now!
My true name is at stake!
Okay, fine. If you insist.
You don't have to sound so bothered!
Normally, in an Application of the Contract,
we would offer each other our true names
and swear to remain together for life.
They're performed at marriage ceremonies.
When I first heard about it, my heart fluttered.
Yet now things have wound up like this.
I never dreamed of doing this with
a man I've only known half a month.
I'm ready. Stand here.
Don't fall asleep!
Oh, sorry.
I thought this would be simpler.
Just stand there. Let's begin.
I will now perform the
Application of the Contract.
From here, it'll be just like last time.
In the name of the great moon deity Muna,
I, Urza Eksess, command you.
I forbid you from sharing
my true name or using it for evil.
Do you swear to this?
I do.
Wh-Wh-What?!
Huh?
What do you think you're doing?!
I thought we sealed the contract with a kiss.
Was I wrong?
That's like a bonus you
do at wedding ceremonies!
The contract is complete
once you swear to its terms!
Oh, really? In that case...
I guess this was an unfortunate accident.
Since we've already got a magic circle,
I shall also perform a contract
with a salamander fire spirit.
What?
My first command is to scorch
the sexual offender before me.
What?!
Why are you three so sleepy?
There was an unfortunate incident.
Shut up. Don't speak of it.
Kyle, you smell burnt.
That was an unfortunate
misunderstanding as well...
I mean, it's nothing.
By the way, we've done
the Application of the Contract,
but can I assume you'll
continue to travel with us?
I have no other choice.
I still haven't heard how or why
you know my true name.
I can't let you out of my sight.
Yeah, sounds like you have no choice.
By the way, I'm sleepy because—
I'm sure you were up late hitting
on women and getting shot down.
Not just up late! I was at it all night long!
City women being easier is a total lie!
Ignore him. Why are we going to Archen next?
Oh, because... Sildonia apparently
has a bit of a prophetic ability.
Huh?
According to the reading,
we should head to Archen next.
A-Ah, yes, indeed. That's right.
I do possess such an ability. Yes.
Really? That reaction seems odd.
Just your imagination.
This is quite a crowd.
Apparently, Princess Milena is
coming to express her condolences.
I've always wanted to see her.
Then we got lucky.
This is my first time seeing her as well.
Here she is.
Princess Milena de Zirgus,
Zirgus's pride and joy...
She's the future queen.
She's as pretty as they say.
She really is.
Are you all right?
Are you unhurt?
Y-Yeah.
What pretty flowers. Thank you.
She's so kind.
I heard she made time in her
busy schedule for this visit.
What a wonderful princess.
Zentos...
Kyle, are you certain it's this princess?
Yeah. Princess Milena is sixteen years old.
She's destined to die two days from now.
Two days from now, in the early morning,
while heading from Archen to Sanes Village,
the princess's caravan gets
attacked by a hydra.
The forests near Archen have always
been infested with monsters,
and Sanes Village was attacked
by a hydra a month ago.
The princess has come to Archen
upon learning of it.
And next, she'll head to the
still dangerous Sanes Village,
only to be cut down on the way there.
People will say it's a tragedy
caused by her goodwill and bad luck,
but if you ask me, it's the natural
outcome of her reckless actions.
There was no funny business
behind it, was there?
Like an assassination made to look
like the work of monsters.
Well, following the princess's death,
there were all kinds of rumors.
The most suspicion was cast upon
the princess's half-brother, Prince Carenas.
As a concubine's child,
he's second in line for the throne.
He benefits the most from her death.
And even more suspiciously,
Prince Carenas is in town right now.
Oh? But no one's talking about that.
He's a shut-in and won't make
public appearances.
How very suspicious.
Well, I said there were rumors, but in the end,
it was deemed an unfortunate accident.
And now you're trying to use
that unfortunate accident?
Yeah. I'll gallantly show up to save
Zirgus's pride and joy when she's in danger.
It'll make the perfect start
to my heroic tale.
Next Time
The Perfect Start to a Heroic Tale
Next time: "The Perfect Start
to a Heroic Tale."